today we are going to talk about the
今天我们要谈的是
spring boot we have here
spring boot ，我们在这里
a lot of things in the key not about
钥匙里有很多东西与
boot how to improve the developer
开机如何改善开发人员
experience with that how many of you is
有多少人的经验
using a spring right now the spring
现在使用弹簧
frivolous itself great how many people
轻浮本身很棒多少人
is using spring boot in production or
在生产中使用 spring boot 或
not many okay this session in this
本届会议没有很多好事
session I'm going to talk the first
会议，我要先谈
minute about spring and spring but in
分钟关于春天和春天但是
general and after that I will I will be
一般，之后我会
I will start coding so let's get start
我将开始编码，让我们开始吧
well my name is 80 Melendez I am java
我的名字是80 Melendez我是Java
software engineer i am from peru I also
我是秘鲁的软件工程师，我也是
on spring a open-source contributor like
在春季，像
Al Kaline cute and many sprint projects
Al Kaline可爱，还有许多冲刺项目
I have been with playing with a with a
我一直在和一个
spring portfolio and I also with the my
春季投资组合，我也与我的
body's spring bootie starter okay I
身体的春季短靴入门我可以
almost saw blogger so the first thing I
差点看到博客，所以我的第一件事
want to talk is about the belapur
要谈的是Belapur
experience as we know we are in we're in
我们所知道的经历
a world which is consumed by software
被软件消耗的世界
software is everywhere every business is
每个企业都无处不在的软件
this built using software and this is
这是使用软件构建的，这是
impacting our daily life like for
像这样影响我们的日常生活
example you were Netflix but we can say
例如您是Netflix，但我们可以说
that programming is changing the world
编程正在改变世界
and we also developers need tools
我们开发人员也需要工具
powerful tools how many of you feel good
功能强大的工具你们当中多少人感觉很好
when are developing applications
何时开发应用程序
do you feel good or do you have to do
您感觉良好还是必须做
many things and you are worried about
很多事情，你担心
that you don't like it using a spring
你不喜欢用弹簧
boot we are going to do to improve our
引导我们将要做的是改善我们的
developer experience so as we know in as
开发人员的经验，如我们所知
we saw in the in the keynote this is the
我们在主题演讲中看到的是
spring ecosystem everything is under the
春季生态系统一切都在
spring framework or and there are
Spring Framework或还有
several projects around eight for a
围绕八个的几个项目
spring web services spring integration
Spring Web服务Spring集成
security data spring batch social and I
安全数据Spring Batch处理社会和我
remember when I start using the spring
记得当我开始使用弹簧时
in I was using the version 2 dot 5 and
在我使用版本2点5和
it was really interesting I guess have
我想这真的很有趣
to create an XML file and keep my class
创建一个XML文件并保留我的课程
and then start injecting all the things
然后开始注入所有东西
that I need this is a spring framework
我需要的是一个Spring框架
we have seeing all the modules and a
我们已经看到了所有模块和一个
spring framework and the consistent
Spring Framework 和一致
provide all the all the ingredients that
提供所有的所有成分
we need as a developer so
我们需要作为开发人员，所以
this is a spring boot who likes cakes
这是喜欢蛋糕的 spring boot
everyone right if you're like a cake so
大家都对，如果您想吃蛋糕，那么
you are going to enjoy with a spring
你将享受春天
boot so but what is the spring boot oh
这样开机，但是春天的开机是什么哦
sorry do you remember this or who is
对不起，你还记得这个吗？
using a spring with XML now okay that's
现在使用带有XML的spring可以了
okay but this is the old fashioned all
好的，但这是老式的
way to configure spraying nowadays in
现在配置喷涂的方式
version 3 yeah see everything can be
版本3是的，看到的一切都可以
configured through java country you can
通过java国家配置可以
use a being annotation and configuration
使用存在注释和配置
out of wire who is using spring with
用弹簧的人
annotations pull so when I swim provide
注释拉动，所以当我游泳时提供
the other configuration but there is
其他配置，但有
that there was a problem when we start
当我们开始时有一个问题
writing applications because we need
编写应用程序，因为我们需要
many many configurations there is
有很多配置
someone who remember who can tell me all
谁记得谁可以告诉我所有人
the steps to to set up a sprint data for
为其设置冲刺数据的步骤
example it's very usual to I don't know
例如，我不知道这很平常
but maybe its usual to open another Pro
但也许通常打开另一个Pro
yet copy the configuration and then copy
尚未复制配置，然后复制
all the dependencies to to my current
对我当前的所有依赖
project and and tried
项目，并尝试
and maybe an error is produced because
可能会产生错误，因为
it's not welcome fuel so in spring boot
不受欢迎的燃料，所以在 spring boot
if we want to configure one data source
如果我们要配置一个数据源
we have seen the XML away the Java
我们已经看到XML不再是Java
configuration way and in spring boot all
配置方式和 spring boot 全部
you have to do is set up all the
您要做的就是设置所有
properties but why spring boot because
属性，但为什么 spring boot ，因为
it's like provide convention over
就像提供约定
configuration all the spring team has
春季团队拥有的所有配置
provide the right configuration for I
为我提供正确的配置
can say almost all the projects oh they
几乎可以说所有项目哦
also provide dependency management who
还提供依赖管理的人
who is happy dealing with dependencies
谁乐于处理依赖关系
not one right sometimes you have you
有时候你没有你的权利
have to choose or you have to find the
必须选择或者您必须找到
right version in order to to give you
正确的版本，以便给您
your application running it provides
您运行它的应用程序提供
auto configuration you just need to tell
您只需要告诉自动配置
a spring boot I want to use web jpa and
我想使用Web JPA的 spring boot 和
everything is going to be configured by
一切都将由配置
itself by spring boot you don't need to
本身通过 spring boot ，您不需要
write code for that that's because
为此编写代码是因为
that's the reason why our developer
这就是为什么我们的开发商
experience is going to improve in the
经验将得到改善
demo during the demo we are going to do
演示过程中的演示
to to see this a starter dependences as
看到这是一个入门依赖
I said dealing with dependencies is hard
我说过处理依赖关系很困难
and the springboard team provide the
跳板队提供
right dependencies to for our
对我们的正确依赖
applications and there are also no
应用程序，也没有
functional requirements and
功能要求和
sometimes is not considered in
有时不考虑
applications but with the spring boot is
应用程序，但与 spring boot 是
is really easy and we are going to to
真的很容易，我们将要
see now the first place to start is this
现在看到的第一个起点是
Web Start dots print I oh so just save
Web Start点打印我哦，所以保存
in your favorites please and this
在您的收藏夹中，这个
website has been built with with the
网站已与
spring boot is an open source project
spring boot是一个开源项目
you can don't go out and see all the
你不能出去看看所有的
configurations all the code maybe you
配置所有代码，也许你
are very familiar with this group
对这个人很熟悉
artifact ID for the build tools like
构建工具（如
Maybin or Grail there are you can choose
可以选择Maybin或Grail
the package jar or war who is using who
包装罐或战争谁在使用谁
is deploying with jars of fat jars two
用两个广口瓶进行部署
three four okay also you can choose the
三四好，你也可以选择
the java version okay spring boot can
Java版本好了 spring boot 可以
run over java one dot six so anyone is
在Java一点六上运行，所以任何人都可以
using java 6 7 8 oh great okay
使用Java 6 7 8哦，很好
and also you can choose the language is
而且您可以选择语言是
not only Jabba you can run over Ruby or
不仅是Jabba，您还可以运行Ruby或
cuddling cuddling was added few months
拥抱几个月被添加
ago here you can tell which projects you
以前在这里你可以告诉你哪些项目
want to use but there are other ways to
想使用，但还有其他方法
start with spring boot it doesn't matter
从 spring boot 开始没关系
where you are even even if you are using
即使您正在使用，也可以在哪里
just your terminal you can say Q
只是你的终端，你可以说Q
and here you are going to see again all
在这里，您将再次看到所有
the ways you can if you can use if you
如果可以的话可以使用的方式
want to use sorry Grail repro yet or
想要使用抱歉的Grail repro还是
maybe built by default is may even pray
也许默认情况下是建造甚至可以祈祷
it all the dependencies it is very well
所有的依赖关系都很好
designed so here you can find some
设计好的，所以您可以在这里找到一些
examples to to download so there are no
要下载的示例，因此没有
excuses to start with with the
借口从
springboard and another thing is with a
跳板，另一件事是与
spring see a lie okay for example I can
春天，例如，我可以撒谎
run I can start very quickly writing
运行，我可以很快开始写作
this this code
这个代码
I'm going to say rest controller + 3
我要说 rest controller + 3
controller
控制者
anyone using the last version of a
任何使用最新版本的
spring for dot three okay there are new
点三的春天，好，有新的
annotations like getmapping simple here
像getmapping这样的注释在这里很简单
welcome to spring one
欢迎来到春天
oh sorry I forgot
哦，对不起，我忘了
Oh yep thank you
哦，是的，谢谢
and now i have my my application of
现在我有我的申请
running over at own cup so we can state
在自己的杯子上跑过去，所以我们可以说
here and is that welcome to spring well
在这里，欢迎春天的到来
yeah a spring but by by itself it's
是的春天，但就其本身而言
depends of its ran over at embedded
取决于它在嵌入式运行
tonka but you can configure it also with
tonka，但您也可以使用
under two and jetty sorry
两岁以下，码头很抱歉
oh there are there are two ways to to
哦，有两种方法可以
run spring boot applications you can run
运行您可以运行的spring boot应用程序
just the jar as a jar file or you can
只是将jar作为jar文件，也可以
also build the war file and then put in
还建立战争文件，然后放入
an another server don't cut or cables or
另一台服务器不切断或电缆连接，或者
whatever you want oh I'm going to talk
随便你，我要说
about that in a few minutes maybe that's
在几分钟之内大概就是
one of it is time so as you can see
其中之一是时间，如您所见
there are different ways to start
有不同的开始方式
through the website through the command
通过网站通过命令
line two but also you can start with
第二行，但你也可以开始
your IDE and we are going to see a same
您的IDE，我们将看到相同的
interface I will use a sword boot
界面我将使用宝剑靴
I'm going to keep the rest so default
我将其余的保留为默认值
and we are going to use the last the
我们将使用最后一个
last version of offspring boot it was
后代靴子的最新版本是
delivered the last week so it's hot I'm
上周送达了，所以我很热
going to tell I want web and jpa
会告诉我我想要Web和JPA
a character provide production-ready
提供生产准备的角色
futures we are going to see this later
期货我们稍后会看到
okay as you can see this is pointing to
好，正如您所看到的，这指向
the star spring hill site I for God but
星光山丘遗址我为上帝而
so few things that we have to check
几件事我们必须检查
before to start coding is that the site
开始编码之前是该站点
is going to provide may be employed with
将提供可能被雇用
everything everything just to start as
一切，一切，从头开始
you can see there is a jar and there is
你可以看到有一个罐子，里面有
a parent in which will bring all the
父母会带来所有
things that the spring needs like all
春天一样需要的东西
the dependencies all the plugins that
依赖所有的插件
already need spring boot already need
已经需要spring boot已经需要
and as you can see i choose web and jpa
如您所见，我选择了Web和JPA
and you cannot find for example a spring
你找不到春天
MVC or embedding Duncan dependency here
MVC或在此处嵌入Duncan依赖项
because with these starters a spring
因为有了这些启动器，春天
provides all the dependencies if I want
提供所有依赖项，如果我想
to dip into sorry
感到抱歉
for example this is the starter and the
例如这是首发，
starter set it's going to use hibernate
初学者设置它将使用休眠
core jdbc aop hibernate entitymanager
核心jdbc aop休眠实体管理器
and there is also attached dependency
并且还有附加的依赖性
and this section is the springboard
这是跳板
mayim mayim plugin which provide more
mayim mayim插件，提供更多
futures to work with the spring book and
与春季书一起工作的期货
there is just one class here i'm going
我要去的只有一堂课
to rename this
重命名这个
alright
好的
okay and the only thing that we need to
好的，我们唯一需要做的就是
run this application is this annotation
运行这个应用程序就是这个注释
spring boot application in which have
Spring Boot应用程序在其中
well is a configuration it has a
好是它有一个配置
configuration annotation and the
配置注释和
component has come which will load all
组件已经到来，将加载所有
the configurations in the same package
同一包中的配置
and packaged packages and under this and
和包装好的包装，在此之下
this annotation the navel and the
这个注释肚脐和
configuration is who who who does the
配置是谁做的
trick to enable all these all this stuff
启用所有这些东西的技巧
all these of the configurations
所有这些配置
i'm going to show you this
我要告诉你这个
here here we can see all the
在这里我们可以看到所有
configurations that spring provide out
弹簧提供的配置
aop rabbit batch catching data Cassandra
aop兔子批次捕获数据Cassandra
coach base and many others spring data
教练基地和许多其他 spring data
projects there are also jdbc mail Flyway
项目中还有jdbc Mail Flyway
like liquid base so we already have jpa
像液体底霜，所以我们已经有了jpa
so the first thing I going to do is
所以我要做的第一件事是
create identity
创建身份
okay i will use by the annotation
好的，我将通过注释使用
generated for you ok
为您生成好
and here I'm going to create my setters
在这里，我将创建我的二传手
and getters
和吸气剂
two
二
I am also going to build one constructor
我还要建立一个构造函数
to save the name and one NT constructor
保存名称和一个NT构造函数
because it's required by jpa anyone
因为JPA任何人都需要
using the spring data JP a few so
使用弹簧数据JP几
speaker
扬声器
push turn
推弯
should be an interface and i'm going to
应该是一个接口，我要去
start a pd repository speaker
启动PD存储库发言人
okay well this interface provide several
好的，这个界面提供了几个
methods like I can find all count safe
像我可以找到所有方法一样安全的方法
this is the the abstraction to work with
这是可以使用的抽象
jpa what now i am going to populate the
jpa现在我要填充什么
sorry i forgot to import the h2 database
对不起，我忘记了导入h2数据库
as you can see i have not said that any
如您所见，我没有说任何
version any version because as i said a
版本任何版本，因为正如我所说
spring would provide the right patient
春天将提供合适的患者
by default and now i am going to use
默认情况下，现在我要使用
only comment 94 near so large speakers
在如此大的发言者附近仅评论94
works
作品
I need the data pendency here pregnant
我需要数据在这里怀孕
ok
好
I don't need to say out of wire here
我不用在这里说
because in the last release of spring in
因为在春季的最后一次发行中
four dot three sprain in yet by default
默认情况下四点三扭伤
in in any configuration for in any
在任何配置中
configuration all the all the
全部配置
dependencies that is required by the
所需的依赖项
class so here
在这里上课
of
的
speaker
扬声器
we're sorry Josh hello
很抱歉，乔希（你好）
speakers
讲者
so I'm going to yet
所以我要去
okay as you can see I have no right any
好的，你可以看到我没有权利
configuration is writing code to the
配置正在将代码写入
labor what my team and I also need a
努力工作我的团队，我也需要一个
speaker sorry can you repeat oh no no it
演讲者抱歉，您可以重复一遍吗？
is not need a springboard by itself
本身不需要跳板
recognized all the repositories now this
现在识别了所有存储库
isn't it it's oh it is not back by by
是不是哦，还没有回来
the by the name of the class is by the
通过类的名称是通过
interface because i am using JPL
界面，因为我正在使用JPL
repository so spring but we're looking
这样的存储库，但我们正在寻找
for in the in mic in my class but all
因为我班上的麦克风
the all the classes with that are
所有的类是
extended by this by this interface and
通过此接口对此进行扩展，并
will be loaded so
将被加载
here
这里
sir
先生
first controller
第一控制人
and
和
the first thing to speak a repository I
首先要说一个仓库
don't need I just need to get through
不需要我只需要通过
the constructor and then
构造函数，然后
sorry
抱歉
this speakers
这个演讲者
so here I can say to is repository final
所以在这里我可以说是存储库最终的
so now i'm going to put going to run my
所以现在我要投入运行
application as you can see there are no
您可以看到没有应用程序
there are no configuration and is spring
没有配置，是弹簧
boat is well integrated with my eight
船与我的八个人很好地融合在一起
ide so you have the option explain boot
IDE，所以你可以选择解释启动
up it's running so as you can see my
它正在运行，以便您可以看到我的
service has been delivered there are no
服务已经交付，没有
configuration is put all my focus in
配置是我所有的重点
right this application ok so the next
对这个应用程序没问题，所以下一个
thing that we are going to do is use
我们要做的是使用
some properties sometimes we need to set
有时我们需要设置一些属性
up another values and in our projects
在我们的项目中建立另一个价值
for example here I want to see all the
例如在这里我想看到所有
SQL like that hibernate is is doing when
像冬眠的SQL正在做什么
one hit the database so I'm going to
一个命中数据库，所以我要
tell true i'm going to restore my app if
说真的，如果要恢复我的应用程序，
you are using a spring too sweet all
你使用的弹簧太甜了
your projects that are using a spring
您使用弹簧的项目
boot are going to be loaded here so i
引导将要在这里加载，所以我
can run again and as you can see to my
可以再次运行，就像你看到的
project is with the label boot
项目带有标签引导
so it has a start and here you can see
所以它有一个开始，在这里你可以看到
that just using one property I can show
我只用一个属性就可以显示
my mysql my sentences but what's happing
我的mysql我的句子，但有什么问题
if i want to to use my own properties
如果我想使用自己的属性
for example sorry let's say i have a
例如，抱歉，我有一个
conference properties and usually when
会议属性以及通常何时
you want to use oh when you want to in
你想使用哦，当你想
get a properties in spring you are using
在您使用的春季获得属性
this annotation okay but with the
这个注释还可以，但是
springboard this has been improved and I
跳板已经得到改善，我
think that is very useful very useful
认为非常有用非常有用
configuration properties and I can set
配置属性，我可以设置
the prefix which is going to be
前缀将是
conferenced for example i'm going to put
例如召开会议，我要把
name and the location and there is a
名称和位置，还有一个
worn in there
穿在那里
and this suggests me that i can add
这表明我可以添加
another dependency which is the
另一个依赖是
configuration processor and now this
配置处理器，现在这个
dependency is going to allow me to to
依赖关系将使我能够
use the my properties provided by this
使用此提供的我的属性
class by this new class for example i
例如，这个新班级
have now conference name a conference
现在将会议名称命名为会议
location resonate explain what platform
位置共鸣说明什么平台
and the conference location is a little
而且会议地点有点
las vegas
拉斯维加斯
I will write something similar
我会写类似的东西
Wow
哇
but here just enable these properties I
但是这里只启用这些属性
have to use another dependency enable
必须使用另一个依赖项启用
configuration properties and I want to
配置属性，我想
tell I want to enable conference
告诉我要启用会议
properties class I'm going to inject it
属性类，我要注入它
here by conference properties properties
在这里按会议属性
Ortiz
奥尔蒂斯
I'm going to sort by going to print a
我将通过打印一个
sorry
抱歉
good name okay okay
好名字好吧好吧
I'm going to restart it up
我要重新启动它
here you can see all the kids that I
在这里你可以看到我所有的孩子
have populating the application
已填充应用程序
properties by default spring boot by
默认情况下的属性spring boot by
default asp reboot is going to to use
默认使用asp重新启动
embedded tongkat as i said okay now i'm
正如我所说的，现在嵌入嵌入式tongkat
going to use another another starter
将要使用另一个新手
because sometimes we want to to build
因为有时候我们想建立
web applications and this time
Web应用程序和这次
i'm going to use tyne leaf and here i'm
我要用泰恩树叶，我在这里
going to cheat a little bit because I
有点作弊，因为我
don't want to write any code for this
不想为此编写任何代码
this is a simple time leaf applique CH
这是一个简单的时间贴花CH
tml and by default springboard it has a
tml，默认情况下，它具有一个
lot of default values and here is a
很多默认值，这是一个
spring is going to read this folder
春天要读这个文件夹
templates and load the speaker HTML file
模板并加载扬声器HTML文件
but it needs it needs one configuration
但它需要一种配置
so speak controller I'm going to
所以说控制器，我要
annotate with controller stove
用控制器灶具注释
and what's happened there
那里发生了什么
and here again
再来一次
so public
如此公开
get mopping
拖地
by going to two speakers
拜访两位发言人
the speakers
演讲者
hmm
嗯
Franco
佛朗哥
now I'm going to render this this new
现在我要渲染这个新的
controller but with time leaf
控制器但有时间片
as you can see a spring boot is not only
如您所见， spring boot 不仅
using a spring pro yet it also encourage
使用spring pro，但它也鼓励
developers to use another tools that are
开发人员可以使用其他工具
well integrated with sprint and now is
与sprint很好地集成在一起，现在
is render with using my HTML file and
使用我的HTML文件渲染
tie live but what about if I want to use
并列，但如果我想使用该怎么办
the last version of time leaf or any
时间片的最新版本或任何
other any other a framework library it's
其他任何其他框架库
really very it is really really easy to
真的非常非常容易
override these properties and in this
覆盖这些属性，在此
version in one for a spring boot
spring boot 合二为一
provides of the configuration 49 lift to
提供配置49电梯至
and I lift three so is only have to do
我举三只所以要做
this
这个
so live way out there the Russian
所以活出那里俄罗斯
sponsor own
赞助者自己
I like to verify here
我想在这里验证
sorry
抱歉
Yannick
亚尼克
it's not working sir
先生不行
let let me check
让我检查一下
there is no typo oh thank you
没有错别字哦，谢谢
and now it's no it's okay thank you as
现在不可以了，谢谢
you can see it's very easy to to
你会发现这很容易
overwrite the these properties but you
覆盖这些属性，但是您
can take care about this because you can
可以照顾这个，因为你可以
break the compatibility between the this
打破这之间的兼容性
dependency this new dependency with the
这个新的依赖与
springboard the springboard team it has
跳板队
working very hard on this all the time
一直在努力工作
they are they are trying to provide the
他们是他们试图提供
last version of these technologies so
这些技术的最新版本
let's restart again now i am using a new
让我们再次重启，现在我正在使用新的
version of time lift this time is still
这次的时间提升版本仍然是
working with the with this new
与这个新的一起工作
dependency but now if we are using a
依赖关系，但现在如果我们使用
time leave week and we want to to modify
时间假星期，我们要修改
this this HTML you have to set up some
这个HTML你必须设置一些
some stats on properties or we can add
一些属性统计信息，或者我们可以添加
another dependency which is dev tools
另一个依赖是开发工具
here
这里
optional true this is just for
可选true，这仅用于
development purpose and with with this
开发目的以及与此
with this dependency we are going to
有了这种依赖性，我们将
enable some kind some stuff like for
启用某种类似的东西
example we are using h2 database I
例如我们正在使用h2数据库
embedded database so we are going to
嵌入式数据库，所以我们要
enable with this dependency another
启用具有此依赖关系的另一个
endpoint and I can dip into the database
端点，我可以深入数据库
now
现在
I have not I just add the dependency and
我不只是添加依赖项而已
now h2 database endpoint is enabled as
现在h2数据库端点已启用为
you can see that the table is right
你可以看到桌子对了
there and the data is social there so
那里的数据是社交的，所以
this is enabled by by this dependency
通过此依赖关系启用
but what about my web page anyone has
但是任何人都有我的网页呢
heard about life reload cool some of you
听说生活重装酷一些
okay with this chrome extension I'm
好的，这个Chrome扩展程序是
going to connect to my application
将要连接到我的应用程序
through a web socket because with this
通过网络套接字，因为与此
dependency left toes man my application
依赖左脚趾男人我的应用程序
going to expose our a WebSocket server
将公开我们的WebSocket服务器
so any change that I will do in my in my
所以我要做的任何改变
app is going to be refresh in this
应用程序将在此刷新
application I am connected right now yes
应用程序我现在已连接是
at the same time
与此同时
for example here
例如这里
platform
平台
and as you can see it has been reload I
如您所见，它已经重新加载了
have not do anything and what happened
什么也没做
this also improved you your experience
这也改善了您的体验
because when we are developing new site
因为当我们开发新网站时
we are all the time modifying this kind
我们一直在修改这种类型
of stuff so we need to prototype very
的东西，所以我们需要非常原型
quickly and start avoid to restart the
快速并开始避免重新启动
application every time but another thing
每次都申请，但另一件事
that the spring boot deck depth tools
spring boot 套深度工具
does is for example if I if I modify my
举例来说，如果我修改我的
java file the iOS to take a space my
iOS的java文件占用空间
application is because we know is
应用是因为我们知道是
reloaded this is because a springboard
重装，这是因为跳板
works with class loaders so any change
与类加载器一起使用，因此任何更改
that I I will do the magma classes in my
我会在我的岩浆班
application it will be reloaded but be
应用程序将被重新加载但
careful because if you are going to add
小心，因为如果要添加
another dependency this is not going to
另一个依赖关系，这不会
work because in in the the first time
工作是因为在第一次
you run all the classes has been loaded
您运行所有类都已加载
so the new dependency is is not there
所以不存在新的依赖关系
yet until do refresh all all all your
直到刷新全部
stuff
东西
okay we have also talked a little bit
好吧，我们也谈了一点
about a production rate futures and
关于生产率期货和
there was a question about actuator what
关于执行器有什么问题
what is so what if we are we are going
那是什么，如果我们要去
to deploy in production and we want
在生产中部署，我们想要
matrix a health status of my application
矩阵我的应用程序的健康状况
or or I want to expose all the
或者或者我想公开所有
configuration that is already there I
我已经存在的配置
think that who is doing this stuff
认为谁在做这个东西
without the springboard who spoke matrix
没有说矩阵的跳板
fell the status ok too but with the
地位也没问题，但是
springboard you just need one dependency
跳板，您只需要一个依赖项
and your application will expose all
您的应用程序将公开所有
this stuff
这个东西
as you can see I just add in some
如您所见，我只是添加一些
configuration some dependencies and all
配置一些依赖和所有
this stuff is is provided by by by booth
这些东西是由摊位提供的
but ok has been refresh
但是还可以
so now I have a new endpoint that has
所以现在我有一个新的端点
been provided by spring boot by these
由这些 spring boot 提供
new dependency here we can see all my
新的依赖关系，我们可以看到我所有的
inviting properties for example it's
邀请属性，例如
loading the application properties that
加载的应用程序属性
is inside of my my pro yet the stuff
在我的专业人士内
that I have there and this stuff this is
我在那里，这个东西是
provided by dev tools as you can see it
如您所见，由开发工具提供
says springwood h2 console enable true
说springwood h2控制台启用true
and tiny lifts catching false that there
和微小的电梯发现那里的错误
are only other stuff but this we are
只是其他东西而我们
using with this right now what about my
现在就用这个​​怎么办
friend status I want to know who my
朋友状态我想知道谁
application is running in and if there
应用程序在其中运行，如果有
are the dependencies are are okay in
依赖关系还可以吗
this case we are using a database a data
在这种情况下，我们正在使用数据库数据
source so it also said that the database
来源，所以它也说数据库
is a h2 and is running and I also have
是h2并且正在运行，我也有
information about my disk space which is
有关我的磁盘空间的信息是
very useful useful there are other
非常有用的有用的还有其他
endpoints like config props I can see
我可以看到类似config props的端点
here all the under configuration
这里所有的配置不足
properties that are more pro yet there
更专业的属性
are metrics spring would provide matrix
春天的指标将提供矩阵
about out of the box
开箱即用
so this is this is awesome if we are
因此，如果我们
going to apply in production we just
要应用于生产中，我们只是
need to add this this dependency but
需要添加此依赖项，但是
what about what if I want to add another
如果我要添加另一个怎么办
health status here I want to customize
我要自定义的健康状况
this this stuff remember i'm going to
这个东西记得我要
add a hell indicator for example
例如添加地狱指示器
so
所以
and maybe I want to add some other stuff
也许我想添加一些其他内容
like one message
像一条消息
spring one is running maybe it's just an
春天正在运行，也许只是
example so sorry
例子很抱歉
I'm going to reload this because i have
我要重新加载，因为我有
added a new dependency
添加了新的依赖
so if we are in the health endpoint we
因此，如果我们处于健康终点，
are going to see this new gear which is
将会看到这个新装备
spring one this key is my method name
春天一，这个关键是我的方法名称
but without the hell indicator okay it's
但如果没有地狱指示，那是
not required to name like this but if
不需要这样命名，但是如果
you prefer to write something like the
您喜欢写类似
spring one health indicator a spring but
春季一个健康指标
will delete this suffix so now what if i
将删除此后缀，所以现在如果我
want what security to my application
想要我的应用程序有什么安全性
again it's really easy you don't have to
再次，您真的很容易
do they open in all this configuration
他们在所有这种配置下打开吗
and looking for dependencies
并寻找依赖
you were to reload this
你要重新加载这个
and by default is you add in this new
默认情况下，您添加了这个新
dependency your application is using
您的应用程序正在使用的依赖项
security if i want to to check the
安全，如果我想检查
speakers page is going to ask me about
扬声器页面会问我有关
my user and password and by default the
我的用户名和密码，默认情况下
username is user and the password is
用户名是用户，密码是
generated and provided in in your law so
在您的法律中生成并提供，因此
I already there but what if I want to
我已经在那里了，但是如果我想
customize I I don't want to enter in
自定义II不想输入
each server and pick the password
每个服务器并选择密码
I don't know what's happening with that
我不知道那是怎么回事
configuration stains blower
配置污渍鼓风机
mhm
嗯
vacation
假期
just
只是
my username was going to be wood and my
我的用户名是木头，而我的
password would too it's not very secure
密码也不太安全
but his
但是他的
I'm going to it another one
我要去另一个
there you know maybe gloat
那里你知道也许幸灾乐祸
Sir Alec move
亚历克爵士的举动
so let's see okay now it is required
现在让我们看看是否需要
what if I right boot and boot here iron
如果我正确引导并在这里引导铁怎么办
inside of my application again and here
再次在我的应用程序内部
you can see that in the first time I
你可以看到我第一次
show the whole employed you can see you
显示整个员工，你可以看到你
could see more information about it but
可以看到有关它的更多信息，但是
once you do define some rolls the spring
一旦定义好一些弹簧
boot will take care about this and you
开机会照顾这个，你
as a user you are only able to see the
作为用户，您只能看到
status but not to see all the other
地位，但看不到其他
stuff because if I suppose my database a
的东西，因为如果我想我的数据库
status or my disk space its provide too
状态或我提供的磁盘空间
much information to two other side so
很多信息给另外两个方面
this is yes this just will show to show
这是肯定的，这将显示
up to the two that mean for example like
最多两个意味着例如
to
至
filth oh sorry and don't
污秽哦，抱歉，不要
you already log it as a does it mean and
您已经将其记录为是，并且
again I am able to see all this stuff
我又能看到所有这些东西
again okay so
再次好吧
this is not the only way to run your
这不是运行您的唯一方法
application you have other stuff like
应用程序还有其他东西
the command line tool for example this
命令行工具例如
is s1p through yep you can use a maven
是s1p到是，您可以使用Maven
because as I'll show at the beginning
因为我会在开始时展示
you have already a spring boot maven
你已经有一个 spring boot 专家
plugin so if you are using maven or
插件，因此，如果您使用的是maven或
Grail who is using great no now adays
如今正在使用很棒的圣杯
few okay it's pretty spring love these
几个好吧，这是春天的美好
technologies and it doesn't matter if
技术，如果没有关系
you are using maven or gray they provide
您正在使用他们提供的Maven或Gray
plug-ins for that and I think that there
插件，我认为那里
is and there are also on an integration
是，也有整合
someone in the in the community thing
社区中有人
that provide this as you can see it's
如您所见，它提供了
running again using my maven plugin but
使用我的Maven插件再次运行，但是
now I want to deliver this to production
现在我想把它交付生产
what I need to do i go to package me pro
我需要怎么做才能打包给我
yet
然而
ok
好
so
所以
here you can see the ESP one demo jar
在这里您可以看到ESP一个演示jar
and another one in which this rename as
另一个将其重命名为
a arena what does mean the field 10
竞技场意味着什么10
sorry this the last one is your issue as
抱歉，最后一个是您的问题，因为
the ECR with your yes your classes the
与您的课程一起使用的ECR
classes that you have been right you
你说得对的课程
have right but this year it contains
有权利，但今年包含
it's called Fatiha because there are
因为有
just inside this year my tongue cut is
就在今年我的舌头切开
embedded there too so I just need to
嵌入在那里，所以我只需要
learn this comment I don't need any
了解此评论，我不需要任何评论
application server as you can see it's a
如您所见，它是一个应用服务器
year so you cannot deploy it in in
年，因此您无法在
another server ok it is running again
好的另一台服务器，它再次运行
sorry
抱歉
so
所以
but if I want to use another embedded
但是如果我想使用另一个嵌入式
server as I said at the beginning by
如我一开始所说的服务器
default is using tongue cut but you can
默认使用切舌，但您可以
use under 2 or Yeti by the way the
根据2或雪人使用方式
spring what is using the last version of
春天正在使用最新版本的
tongue cut eight dot five dot 4 so it's
舌头切成八点五点四，所以
school because there are many many
学校，因为有很多很多
futures in these versions and I think
这些版本的期货，我认为
that there are another talk about about
还有另一种谈论
it about Don cut in this thing route so
关于唐的事情就这样切开了
if I want to use another another
如果我想换另一个
embedded server I just need to exclude
嵌入式服务器我只需要排除
here
这里
hood and i will use under two
引擎盖，我将在两个以下使用
spring good structure to I sorry I am
春季结构良好，对不起
excluding here
不包括在这里
yep
是的
yep and i will at the undertow server
是的，我将在Underwow服务器上
yes like this
是这样的
um
嗯
yes reload
是的，重新加载
and as you can see here under 2 has been
如您所见，这里2下是
started in the same port 8080 just to
在相同的端口8080中开始
verify that this my application running
验证此我的应用程序正在运行
everything it is running ok so the
一切运行正常，所以
springboard team has has done a nice
跳板队做得很好
work with that supporting all these
与支持所有这些的工作
embedded so oh sure there is a lot of
嵌入式，所以哦，肯定有很多
abstraction here so what if i want to
抽象在这里，如果我想
change this the server port I just need
更改此服务器端口我只需要
to use my application port and said for
使用我的应用程序端口，并说
example 8082 let's roll out
示例8082，让我们推出
80-82 just to make sure about this hey
80-82只是为了确保这个嘿
kid
小子
oh gee okay the question is how can i
哦，好吧，问题是我怎么能
use another application property file
使用另一个应用程序属性文件
yeah you can use profiles with the
是的，您可以将配置文件与
spring so spring itself without the
春天，所以春天本身没有
spring would provide profiles so you can
春天会提供配置文件，所以你可以
reuse this all this stuff here in spring
在春天在这里重复使用所有这些东西
boot but what if I want to this is sing
启动，但是如果我要唱歌
in my machine but what if I want to
在我的机器上，但是如果我想
deliver this year and deployed winning
交付今年并部署获胜
another in another server with another
另一个在另一个服务器上
properties I'm going to copy the the jar
属性，我要复制罐子
file and put it here and I already have
文件并放在这里，我已经有
sorry
抱歉
I already have this application general
我已经有这个应用程序了
okay and my yard is inside
好吧，我的院子在里面
okay my yard and this new file is there
好吧，我的院子，这个新文件在那里
so the value is now server port 8083
所以现在的值是服务器端口8083
just
只是
you can you can set up new properties
您可以设置新属性
using an application Yemen and overwrite
使用也门应用程序并覆盖
all these all the properties that are
所有这些都是
inside of your jar here is 80 83 so just
你的罐子里是80 83所以
to recap we have seen a spring booting
回顾一下，我们已经看到了 spring boot
action we don't need any any
我们不需要任何动作
configuration all this stuff is this
配置所有这些东西是这个
deal with it config with the spring boot
用Spring Boot处理它的配置
itself it provides the dependency
它本身提供了依赖性
management so yes enjoy with the last
管理，是的，喜欢上一次
version of all the tea party
所有茶话会的版本
dependencies and spring project itself
依赖和Spring项目本身
you can override the properties versions
您可以覆盖属性版本
and you can use the last the last stuff
你可以用最后的东西
sometimes I know that companies refuse
有时候我知道公司拒绝
to to upgrade and they prefer to keep
升级，他们更喜欢保持
the same stuff working on your
同样的东西在你的身上
application but you can also downgrade
应用程序，但您也可以降级
overriding the dependent the property
覆盖从属财产
you can use a spring boot as a year but
您可以使用 spring boot 作为一年，但
there are there are another option and
还有另一种选择，
you can and you can build a wall okay
你可以，你可以盖墙好
there is no too much time to do this but
没有太多的时间去做，但是
the spring would provide a very well
春天会提供一个很好的
documentation so or if you want to to
这样的文档，或者如果您想
talk about that later we can catch up it
稍后再说，我们可以赶上
also provides the actuator with a lot of
还为执行器提供了很多
matrix you can override them you can't
矩阵，您可以覆盖它们，您不能
sorry you can add more more
抱歉，您可以添加更多
configuration to this actuator staff
此执行器人员的配置
logging do you can set up using the
日志记录，您可以使用
application properties keep just look
应用程序属性保持外观
for the keys
对于键
you can override a configuration to
您可以覆盖配置以
maybe we can talk about that later okay
也许我们以后再谈吧
just to finish just enjoy with the
只是为了完成就享受
springboard it provides a really nice
跳板，它提供了一个非常好的
developing developer experience as you
与您一起发展开发人员的经验
can see i have not configured anything
可以看到我没有配置任何东西
is at the dependency and write code
在依赖项并编写代码
because is that matter my application
因为那是我的申请
thank you so much
非常感谢
you
您